(this.webpackJsonpquizlet=this.webpackJsonpquizlet||[]).push([[0],{11:function(e,t,i){},12:function(e,t,i){"use strict";i.r(t);var s=i(1),o=i.n(s),n=i(4),a=i.n(n),r=i(2),c=i(5),h=i(0),u=function(e){var t=e.index,i=e.selected,s=e.answer,o=e.onclick,n=e.answered,a=e.isCorrectAnswer;return Object(h.jsx)("div",{onClick:function(){n||o(t)},className:"answer ".concat(t===i?"selected":""," ").concat(n?a?"correct-answer":"incorrect-answer":""),children:"".concat(s," ").concat(n?a?"\u2714\ufe0f":"\u274c":"")})},d=function(e){var t=Object(s.useState)(""),i=Object(r.a)(t,2),o=i[0],n=i[1],a=Object(s.useState)(!1),c=Object(r.a)(a,2),d=c[0],l=c[1],m=e.index,f=e.question,b=e.answers,p=e.correctAnswer,w=e.feedback,v=e.setCorrectAnswers,y=e.correctAnswers,g=e.questionsAnswered,j=e.setQuestionsAnswered,k=e.setCurrentQuestion,x=e.isFinalQuestion,O=e.setFinished,A=o===p;return Object(h.jsxs)("div",{className:"question",children:[Object(h.jsxs)("div",{className:"question-number",children:["Question ",m+1]}),Object(h.jsx)("div",{className:"question-title",children:f}),Object(h.jsxs)("div",{className:"answers-container",children:[" ",b.map((function(e,t){var i=Object.keys(e)[0],s=Object.values(e)[0],a=i===p;return Object(h.jsx)(u,{isCorrectAnswer:a,index:i,selected:o,answered:d,answer:s,onclick:n},t.toString())}))]}),Object(h.jsxs)("div",{className:"buttons-container",children:[Object(h.jsx)("div",{className:"submit",onClick:function(){!d&&o&&(l(!0),j(g+1),A&&v(y+1))},children:"Submit"}),d&&!x&&Object(h.jsx)("div",{className:"next",onClick:function(){return k(m+1)},children:"Next"}),d&&x&&Object(h.jsx)("div",{onClick:function(){return O(!0)},className:"finish",children:"Finish"})]}),d&&Object(h.jsx)("div",{className:"feedback ".concat(A?"correct":"incorrect"),children:w})]})},l=c.a,m=function(){var e=Object(s.useState)(0),t=Object(r.a)(e,2),i=t[0],o=t[1],n=Object(s.useState)(0),a=Object(r.a)(n,2),c=a[0],u=a[1],m=Object(s.useState)(0),f=Object(r.a)(m,2),b=f[0],p=f[1],w=Object(s.useState)(!1),v=Object(r.a)(w,2),y=v[0],g=v[1],j=(l[i],l.map((function(e,t){var i=e.question,s=e.answers,n=e.correctAnswer,a=e.feedback,r=t===l.length-1;return Object(h.jsx)(d,{index:t,question:i,answers:s,correctAnswer:n,feedback:a,setCorrectAnswers:p,correctAnswers:b,questionsAnswered:c,setQuestionsAnswered:u,setCurrentQuestion:o,isFinalQuestion:r,setFinished:g},t.toString())})));return Object(h.jsxs)("div",{className:"content",children:[!y&&j[i],y&&Object(h.jsxs)("div",{className:"finished-container",children:[Object(h.jsx)("div",{children:"\ud83d\ude4c\ud83d\ude4c\ud83d\ude4c"}),Object(h.jsx)("div",{children:"Thank you for your response"}),Object(h.jsxs)("div",{children:["You got"," ",Object(h.jsxs)("b",{children:[b,"/",c]})," ","questions correct!"]})]})]})};i(11);a.a.render(Object(h.jsx)(o.a.StrictMode,{children:Object(h.jsx)("div",{className:"content-container",children:Object(h.jsx)(m,{})})}),document.getElementById("root"))},5:function(e){e.exports=JSON.parse('{"a":[{"question":"Over the counter fish oil is often advertised as essential to healthy heart function and immunity. If someone you know has high blood pressure or is immune compromised, should you recommend that they:","answers":[{"one":"Supplement their prescription medication with fish oil because it can\u2019t hurt and may well help"},{"two":"Substitute fish oil for their prescription medication and see which makes them feel better"},{"three":"Ignore the advertisement and continue with their prescribed medication"},{"four":"Read what the Natural Medicine Journal says about the value of fish oil"}],"correctAnswer":"three","feedback":"While there are conditions for which fish oil can be recommended by a doctor, fish oil can be dangerous to someone with a heart condition\u2014for example, if they have a defibrillator inserted, it can cause irregular heartbeats\u2014and it can lower the body\u2019s immune response. Many over-the-counter fish oils contain contaminants that are harmful to the body or simply costly and ineffective. See, for example, https://www.webmd.com/vitamins/ai/ingredientmono-993/fish-oil"},{"question":"True or False: Vitamins, supplements, and alternative therapies that are sold in supermarkets or advertised in the media must be subject to the same kinds of randomised clinical trials as prescription medications.","answers":[{"one":"True"},{"two":"False"}],"correctAnswer":"two","feedback":"Research into the efficacy of vitamins is often \u201cmixed\u201d. Clinical trials of the effects of multivitamins on cancer, for example, have not resulted in clear evidence of benefits. See https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/17209217/"},{"question":"What is the primary purpose of doctors prescribing medications?","answers":[{"one":"To make you feel 100% better as soon as possible"},{"two":"To take your money"},{"three":"To promote health, improve quality of life, and prevent harm"},{"four":"To track your whereabouts"}],"correctAnswer":"three","feedback":"While it is the doctor\u2019s job to care for your wellbeing, there are also protections and regular reviews that are conducted to ensure this is being done appropriately. You can find out more about the Australian Medical Board here: https://www.medicalboard.gov.au/.  Additionally, because it is hard to see exactly what is happening inside your body, it is important to remember that treatment is often not a quick fix. "},{"question":"Which of these is not a reason why the Australian government has a Pharmaceutical Benefits Scheme (PBS) which subsidises the cost of prescription medications?","answers":[{"one":"They want timely, reliable and affordable access for all Australians to medications to achieve optimal health and economic objectives"},{"two":"Serious health issues cost the healthcare system more than preventative or maintenance prescriptions"},{"three":"It prevents people taking dangerous medications without medical supervision"},{"four":"They are in the pockets of big pharmaceutical companies"}],"correctAnswer":"four","feedback":"If you want to learn more about how the Australian government prevents pharmaceutical companies from taking advantage of its citizens, or how the PBS works see: https://www.aph.gov.au/Parliamentary_Business/Committees/Senate/Former_Committees/freetrade/report/final/ch04 "},{"question":"Jim stops taking his antibiotics for a persistent infection against his doctor\u2019s wishes because he thinks a more \u2018natural\u2019 option like vitamins is healthier for him. When he starts to feel better, he\u2019s convinced the vitamins cured him. What is the most likely explanation for his feeling better?","answers":[{"one":"Jim had already taken enough medication to start feeling better"},{"two":"The vitamins have cured his condition"},{"three":"Jim\'s doctor\'s original diagnosis was wrong"},{"four":"The medication was making his condition worse, not better, and so once Jim stopped, he began to feel better"}],"correctAnswer":"one","feedback":"It\u2019s easy to think that once you start to feel better you are cured, and just as easy to attribute it to alternative medicines. However, feeling better does not mean you are cured and can just mean the condition will return with greater severity. Prescriptions are designed not only to make you feel better but to eliminate the condition entirely or prevent it from returning. For more information see: https://www.fda.gov/drugs/special-features/why-you-need-take-your-medications-prescribed-or-instructed"},{"question":"Which of these statements about vitamins and supplements is true?","answers":[{"one":"Vitamins can\u2019t cause harm because they are natural"},{"two":"Vitamins should be taken with other prescriptions to give them a boost"},{"three":"If millions of people take vitamins, they must work"},{"four":"Vitamins and supplements cost Australians $5.6 billion annually, can cause serious health conditions, and can reduce the effectiveness of prescription treatments"}],"correctAnswer":"four","feedback":"To see more about the efficacy, dangers, and costs of vitamins and supplements see: https://www.nps.org.au/australian-prescriber/articles/the-safety-of-commonly-used-vitamins-and-minerals"},{"question":"True or false: If a medication lists side effects, it is important to reduce the amount you take it to reduce the risk of the adverse effect occurring","answers":[{"one":"True"},{"two":"False"}],"correctAnswer":"two","feedback":"Side-effects are labelled or explained with prescriptions because healthcare professionals want to give you as much information as possible to be prepared for the minor or rare phenomena that have occurred with other people who received the medication. In most cases, by taking the prescription as instructed you reduce the chance of adverse effects occurring. See here for more information: https://www.healthdirect.gov.au/medicine-and-side-effects"},{"question":"True or False: Because alternative medicines like vitamins and supplements are advertised and prescriptions aren\u2019t, they must be more effective","answers":[{"one":"True"},{"two":"False"}],"correctAnswer":"two","feedback":"Answer: Prescription medication is designed to target very specific conditions that are often complicated or rare, thus making them not marketable to the public. In some cases, they can also become dangerous when used inappropriately. With these reasons in mind, it is important to remember that opinions on the efficacy of a treatment should always be based on experimental results and not media representation."},{"question":"Which of these facts about people not taking their medications regularly or not finishing the course of medications is most true?","answers":[{"one":"Not finishing a course of antibiotics can cause the bacteria causing the illness to become resistant to that antibiotic"},{"two":"The economic costs of non-adherence in Australia have been conservatively estimated to cost tax-payers around $10.4 billion annually (about $517 per person)"},{"three":"Around 10% of hospitalizations in older adults are attributed to medication non-adherence"},{"four":"All of the above"}],"correctAnswer":"four","feedback":"If you would like to find out more information about the negative impact of medication non-adherence on both the individual and societal level see here: https://www.uts.edu.au/about/graduate-school-health/pharmacy/news/1.9-billion-savings-australia-uncovered-new-study or here: https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC6537038/"},{"question":"If you have questions about a prescription and how often you should take it, who should you consult?","answers":[{"one":"The internet"},{"two":"Your friends"},{"three":"You know what\'s best for your body"},{"four":"Your pharmacist or doctor"}],"correctAnswer":"four","feedback":"Healthcare professionals are the most consistent and reliable source of health-related information. It is currently easier than ever to access such assistance with the introduction of telehealth. Find out more here: https://www.digitalhealth.gov.au/initiatives-and-programs/telehealth"}]}')}},[[12,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.7a4501ea.chunk.js.map